Narrator: 3
Speaker: England, English
Narrator: 6
Speaker: Ireland, Irish
Narrator: 2
Speaker: Poland, Polish
Narrator: 5
Speaker: Scotland, Scottish
Narrator: 1
Speaker: Spain, Spanish
Narrator: 4
Speaker: Türkiye, Turkish
Narrator: 9
Speaker: Germany, German
Narrator: 7
Speaker: Mexico, Mexican
Narrator: 8
Speaker: the United States, American
Narrator: 14
Speaker: Argentina, Argentinian
Narrator: 18
Speaker: Australia, Australian
Narrator: 10
Speaker: Brazil, Brazilian
Narrator: 12
Speaker: Egypt, Egyptian
Narrator: 11
Speaker: Hungary, Hungarian
Narrator: 16
Speaker: India, Indian
Narrator: 13
Speaker: Italy, Italian
Narrator: 17
Speaker: Nigeria, Nigerian
Narrator: 15
Speaker: Russia, Russian
Narrator: 20
Speaker: China, Chinese
Narrator: 19
Speaker: Japan, Japanese
Narrator: 21
Speaker: Vietnam, Vietnamese
Narrator: 24
Speaker: the Czech Republic, Czech
Narrator: 22
Speaker: France, French
Narrator: 23
Speaker: Switzerland, Swiss